http://www.agliff.org/privacy-policy

0
We respect each site visitor’s right to personal privacy. To that end, we collect and use information throughout our website only as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. This statement applies solely to information collected on this website.For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.The information we collect is:•used to improve the content of our Web page.•used to notify visitors about updates to our Web site.This website is hosted by Squarespace.  Every time a visitor accesses a site hosted by Squarespace, Squarespace records some non-personally-identifying information, such as the type of browser the visitor is using. Also, Squarespace stores cookies on the computers of visitors to the sites they host. See the Cookies section below for more information about cookies. Some of the information that Squarespace stores is made available to aGLIFF via the Squarespace visitor statistics dashboard. Also, if you post a comment on this website, then whatever information you enter gets stored by Squarespace and can be accessed by aGLIFF, and (if the comment gets approved) future website visitors.  The Squarespace Privacy Policy has more details about the information they collect and how they handle that information.Certain information is required when filling out our voluntary opt-in contact forms, or to submit a film, but we never give away this information. It is only gathered to reply to the sender’s message or to keep you aware of film festival news or updates or that of partner festivals.Please note that when filling out the contact or submission forms, you are opting-in to be added to our mailing list.  You will always be able to opt out of this list when you receive an email from us -- but we suggest you don't, or you may miss valuable information about your current or future submissions.  NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement.CONTACT INFORMATION If site users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please email us.
A Timeline of LGBTQ+ Film
Code of Conduct
Press
Privacy Policy
Contact
Subscribe to our Newsletter
First Name
Last Name
Email Address
Sign Up
Thank you!
This project is supported in part by the Cultural Arts Division of the City of Austin Economic Development Department. 2020 Festival: August 6-16, 2020 aGLIFF © 2018 | All Rights ReservedPolari, Inc., DBA aGLIFFPO Box 49249Austin, TX  78765
